JOYI YAP

♀ 3 Bottega Close, Flat Bush, Auckland, New Zealand

joyiyap19@gmail.com

**** 02108815311

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

I am an ambitious front end developer with 3 years of experience in front end web developing. Graduated as a mulitimedia designer and after 1 year working as a designer I have developed an excellent eye for details which effectively help me to deliver better front end work. I am looking for a progressive organisation to utilise my knowledge and develop my skill-set furthur.

STRENGTHS

- · Working experience as Multimedia Designer
- Proficient in Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator
- Proficient in HTML, CSS, Javascript, jquery
- · Understanding of mobile-first and responsive design
- · Experienced in Bootstrap framework

- Experienced in using CMS (Adobe AEM, Wordpress)
- Beginner in Git
- · Beginner in npm, gulp, scss
- · Beginner in ReactJS

WORK HISTORY

APD Group Malaysia

Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia May 2017 - Dec 2017

Front End Developer

- Maintained and customised website on Adobe Experience Manager (AEM) under company guidelines.
- Developed responsive web pages using HTML/HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript and JQuery.
- Created HTML email templates and newsletters for e-mail marketing campaigns.
- Tested front-end code in multiple browsers and fixed issues to ensure cross-browser compatibility.
- Coordinated with team of front-end developers to ensure quality of website and client satisfaction before deployment.

Consider iProspect

Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia Dec 2014 - Mar 2017

Front End Developer

- Developed fully functional responsive prototypes based on requirements using HTML/HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript and JQuery.
- Integrated approved prototypes in Wordpress utilizing Wordpress theme and plugins.
- Tested front-end code in multiple browsers and fixed issues to ensure cross-browser compatibility.

Creative Tomato Design & Digital Kitchen

Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia Mar 2014 - Oct 2014

Graphic and Web Designer

- · Created interface designs for integration into web applications.
- Created graphic designs for social postings, social ads, social banners, brochures and press ads.

QUALIFICATIONS

The One Academy of Arts and Communications

Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia 2010 - 2013

Ave Maria Convent

Ipoh, Malaysia 2005 - 2009

Diploma in Multimedia Design

 Developed knowledge and various digital skills from user experience and interface design to web development and video production.

SPM (Sijil Pelajaran Malaysia)

· Malaysian Certificate of Education

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Communication skills

- · Proficient in spoken and written English.
- · Native speaker of Mandarin and Cantonese.
- · Basic communication skills in Korean. (Level 2 in TOPIK Proficiency Test).

Date of Birth

19 February 1992

Interests

- · An outgoing person who enjoys running.
- · Love travelling, exploring new places and experience different cultures.
- · Love watching good films.

REFERENCES AVAILABLE ON REQUEST